Kaiji took advantage of Sakazaki's rampage to sneak into Ichijou's room!
坂崎が暴れている隙に
一条の部屋に忍び込んだカイジ
だが！凶器の制裁
血のマニキュア！
But he receives the brutal punishment of a blood manicure!
クソッ！チキショウ！
Dammit!
Goddammit!
一条の野郎
Ichijou, you bastard!
そしてシャバでの最終日！
And today is his final day on the outside!
Very well. I accept your challenge.
いいだろう　受けてやる
その挑戦
最初で最後の沼との死闘
Kaiji's first and last battle with the Bog!
Prelude to the Showdown
残された時間 あと７時間！
He has only seven hours left!
てっ 店長…
Boss!
心配するな　恐れることはない
Don't worry. Nothing can possibly go wrong.
俺の沼は
ちょっとした思いつきやアイデア
So what if he things he's figured out the Bog?
そんな付け焼き刃で
どうかなる代物じゃない
His ego isn't going to get him anywhere.
違うか？
そ… それはそうですが…
Right?
Er, yes, but...
So it's nothing but fifty million in our pockets.
となりゃ落ちてるじゃないか
5000万
拾っとこうぜ
There's no reason to hold back. Kaiji's finished when he loses this money.
臆することはない
この金を失えば
さすがのカイジくんもアウツ
玉砕！決定する
Ruined! Completely bust!
He'll live the rest of his life in that abyss!
生涯 あの地獄の住人に
フフフ…
もう拝まずに済むってわけだ
After that, I'll never have to see his face again!
その暑苦しい顔を
フッ いいだろう
やってやれ 磁気チェックだ
Go ahead and check him for magnets.
Hold still, okay?
いいか 動くなよ
店長 電話です
Boss!
Phone call from Mr. Kurosaki.
黒崎さまから
黒崎さま？
Mr. Kurosaki? This early?
こんな時間に…
はい 一条です
すまんな 朝っぱらから
Hello, Ichijou speaking.
Sorry to bother you so early in the morning.
いえ
Don't worry about it.
実は老婆心ながら
ふと気になってな
I've gotten a bit worried about today.
今日なんだ　今日が最終日
Today's his final day.
The last day Kaiji will ever spend above ground.
あのカイジという男が
地上にいられる最後の日
I seem to recall his time limit ending at four in the afternoon.
確か 今日の午後４時が
タイムリミットと記憶しておるが
奴なら来てます
Yes. He's here.
来てる？
ええ
Oh, he came?
Yes.
And you let him in?
入れたのか？
はい
Yes.
バカ！軽率だな
You moron.
You're too careless!
Am I?
そうでしょうか？
入れはしましたが問題ありません
There should be no problem letting him in!
沼は完全無欠
究極の最強マシーンです
The Bog is invincible! It's the ultimate machine!
奴は必ず負けます！
愚か者！
He'll lose for sure!
Fool!
That confidence is dangerous!
その自信こそが一番危険なのだ
沼に固執していた奴が
あの台を打つということは
If he's playing the Bog, he has to have something planned!
勝算があるからだ
恐らく５割強は
Probably something that gives him better than 50-50 odds!
バカな！あり得ません
そんなことは
That's impossible!
Fine.
まあいい
勝算がありかなしか そんなことを
今ここで話しても仕方ない
At this point, it doesn't matter whether he has a plan or not.
こうなった以上 勝つしかない
もちろんです
All we have to do is win.
Of course!
Don't think that you can simply lose that 600 million and still keep your position.
メンツうんぬんも さることながら
現在 たまってる６億を超える大金
負けましたと言って
済まされる額ではない
If you lose it, I'm going to have to make an example of you.
万が一 負けた場合は
お前に過酷かつ破滅的な処遇を
課すしかない
Understand?
いいな？
構いません
That won't be a problem!
そうか
その覚悟があればいいんだ
I see. As long as you understand exactly what you're doing.
勝てよ 一条　生きるために
Win, Ichijou.
If you want to survive.
It has arrived!
ついに来る
Kaiji's first and last challenge!
カイジ 最初で最後の挑戦！
He risks it all on this pivotal moment!
全てを懸け
満を持して迎えたこの時
This is his last chance to stay above ground!
これが地上での生を懸けた
ラストチャンス！
バカが！出るわけがない
That idiot! The Bog will never pay out!
あの沼が！
買いかぶりすぎなんだ 黒崎さまは
Mr. Kurosaki worries too much about him!
There's no way he's that far beyond me!
奴は俺より はるかに格下！
パッキーだ
はっ
Paqy.
まず1000万
えっ 1000万？
Ten million.
Ten million!?
マジかよ？
どうぞ
Really!?
Here you go.
Why's he doing this?
なんでやるかね？
出っこねえのになあ
It ain't gonna pay out.
カ… カイジくん！
Kaiji!
いいんだな 一条　幕を開けるぜ
All right, Ichijou.
Let's raise the curtain on our first and final duel.
俺とお前の最初で最後の真剣勝負
後戻りなしだ
どっちが滅びるにしても
There's no turning back. No matter who's destroyed.
フッ いいから始めろ さっさと
Fine, whatever. Just get started.
思い知らせてやる　お前の傲慢
I'll show you your hubris!
Your weakness!
お前の脆弱！
ゆえに生まれた この沼の隙！
The chink it opened in the Bog's armor!
何だ？
今 入ったぞ
He got one in!
あっ また… また入ったぜ
Another one!
寄ってるじゃないか 今日は！
Today must be a good day!
こりゃあ ひょっとすると
ひょっとするぜ
He just might pull it off!
どっ どういうことだ？
What's going on!? Aren't the pins set to "C"!?
釘設定はＣのはずだろ
もちろんです　今朝ちゃんと
チェックしましたから
Of course! I checked them this morning!
じゃあ あれは何だ？
きてるじゃないか 何度も
Then what's going on!? He's getting far too many in!
そっ それはその… さっぱり
I haven't the foggiest.
きた きた きた！
今日１回目のクルーン
There we go! His first tray today!
惜しかったー
でも いけるいける
Aww!
He's still doing good, though!
どうします？念のため
発動しときますか？例のﾌﾞﾛｯｸを
What do we do? Shall we activate the block to be safe?
いや このギャラリー注視の中で
それはあまりしたくない
No. I don't want to do it when he has that much of an audience.
Even without it, they're suspicious.
それでなくても今
客の不信感が強い
この間 坂崎を殺す時
ちょっと やりすぎたからな
We were too obvious when we finished off Sakazaki.
The block at the second obstacle is especially blatant.
特に第２関門のブロックが
露骨すぎた
Not now.
今はダメだ　まっ 釘の森と
第２関門を抜けても
Even if he makes it through the pins and the gate, there's still the trays.
まだクルーンがある
Those are bulletproof. We're fine.
あそこは鉄壁！何の問題もない
それより 気に入らないのはあれだ
What I'm more worried about...
The pins are set to "C", right!?
釘の設定がＣなんだから
考えられる可能性は１つ
I can only think of one possibility.
あっ！ああ そうか
That's it!
持ってこい
はっ はい！
Bring me it.
Yes, sir!
フフフ… ではお引き取り願うか
小悪党に
Now to take out the trash.
あ？
そこまでだ
That's enough.
中止だ　この勝負は中止！
Stop! You're finished!
ええっ？
なっ なんで？
Why?
Why, Ichijou?
どういうことだ 一条？
フフフ… 不満かい？
不満も何も
Problem?
This just isn't right! You're playing dirty!
メチャクチャじゃねえか！
きたねえぞ
そっちの思惑通り
運んでる時はいいが
You don't get to just stop games when things don't go how you planned!
ちょっとでも計算外のことが
起こると中止 取りやめなんて
Do you really want your casino to get a reputation for that kind of thing?
そんな理不尽を強いるのか
このカジノは？
おいおい 何を言う
当カジノは公正だ
Whatever are you saying? We're perfectly fair.
何が起ころうと打ち出した以上
やめるやめないは打ち手の判断
No matter what happens, the choice to stop or continue is up to the player.
納得のいくまで
勝負していただいて結構
They're allowed to play until completely satisfied.
Then—
なら…
ただし それは
But that's only if they're playing clean.
不正のない場合に限る
えっ？
If they happen to be cheating...
ゴト行為が明らかな場合は…
ちょっ ちょっと待て
何だ そのゴト行為って？
Wait, what do you mean "cheating?"
Pachinko machines are just that. Machines.
パチンコってのは １も２も３も台
台さえ きちんと
管理していれば安全
As long as the machine's operating properly, everything is fine.
問題ないと考えがちだ
だから監視カメラを増やしてまで
工作 細工を阻止しようとする
That's why we've made sure that no one could modify it. We even added security cameras.
But there is one method of doing so that no one expects.
だが意外なことに 台以外のものに
工作 細工されるとは誰も思わない
意識の外　そういう意味で
カイジくんの狙いは悪くない
It was a clever idea, Kaiji.
You're just unlucky that you're not the first person who's tried it.
カイジくんにとって
不運だったのは
かつて同じことをやった奴がいた
ということだ
ええっ？
カイジくんが今やっているゴト
You're cheating... by replacing the balls with smaller ones!
小玉への玉のすり替え
What!?
なっ 何言ってんだ？
それしかないんだよ
It's obvious. Setting "C" is packed the tightest of all, but you're still slipping balls through.
設定Ｃという厳しい釘なのに
バンバンその狭い空間を
くぐり抜けて真ん中に寄っていく
となれば通常より玉が小さいと
考えるしかない
That means you must be using small balls.
I don't know when you slipped into our storage and replaced the Bog balls,
カイジくんが いつどうやって
別のビルにある補充用の沼の玉を
小玉にすり替えたかは不明だが
まっ 台に細工するよりは
はるかに易しい仕事と言える
but I'm sure it was easier than breaking the Bog would have been.
ふざけんじゃねえ
言いがかりだ！
Bullshit! You're making that up!
店長
いい加減なこと 抜かすな！
Boss!
Don't just lie like that!
フフフ… 問答無用
There's no point in complaining.
調べれば分かる
Let me show you. The holes in this plate are the size of normal balls.
この検査板の穴は 本来の
ﾊﾟﾁﾝｺの玉と同じ直径になっている
If your balls fit through this plate, they're small balls.
もし この板の穴を
玉が抜けるようなら
それは通常より小さい
小玉ってことだ
残念だが お前の進撃もこれまで
Sadly for you, this is as far as you'll get.
お… 落ちない？
バカな… どうして…
They're not falling! Why!?
何だよ 問題ねえじゃねえか
Wait, they're fine!
He's fine!
セーフだ セーフだ！
何だ びっくりさせやがる
Don't scare me like that, Kaiji!
カイジくん
ああ！
Okay!
じゃあ続けさせてもらうぜ 一条
遠慮なくな
So I can go back to playing, right?
All right, guys! I don't know what that was about, but here I go again!
みんな 変な水が入ったが再開だ
今日はきてる
マジで見せられるかもしれねえぜ
I just might show it today!
この沼の爆発 大当たりを！
This Bog's jackpot!
いけ！
見せてくれ 大当たりを！
Let's see that jackpot!
こんな… バカな…
How is this happening!?
いけ　いけ　いけ　いけ…
Go! Go! Go! Go!
どうなってるんだ？
What's going on!?
If they don't fit through the plate, does that mean they're real!?
この検査板を抜けないってことは
正常ってことか
今の あの玉
いや待て　待てよ
No, wait! Maybe the plate itself is fake!
そもそも この検査板そのものが
偽物！
If he was in there, he could have replaced the plate too!
造作もないことだ
ありかさえ突き止めていれば
検査板をすり替えることなど…！
Wait, boss!
ああ 店長！
If it has smaller, then normal balls will sit higher in it!
もし検査板の穴が
通常より小さいなら
当然 正常な玉は
きっちり はまらずに
やや出っ張り気味に浮き上がる！
おお… 正常だ　正常
It's the real thing...
なぜだ　一体どうして？
Why? What's going on!?
Why do they pass the pins? Why do they enter the gate!?
なんで寄る？なんで入る？
Normal balls should never make it through setting "C!"
正常な玉で設定Ｃだぞ
入るわけがない！
入るはずがないんだ！
It's impossible!
All right!
きたきた！
またクルーンにきた！
Here we go!
He got another one in the trays!
クソッ！
Damn!
沼を再開して３日
It's been three days since we set the Bog back up. No one could have rigged it so soon.
細工どころか
触られてもいないのに
それは日課の釘チェックでも
確認済み
Plus, we check the pins daily!
おとといは村上 昨日は俺
The last three days have been Murakami, me, and Murakami again.
今朝は村上がチェックした
釘に問題はない
It should be fine!
クッ… 一体…
What the...
フッ… 村上の奴
ずいぶんきつく閉めてやがる
Man, Murakami, you sure pack them tight.
Murakami!
村上
は？
今朝はどうだった？
え？
How was this morning?
釘だよ 釘の調整
どんな感じだった？
The pins! How did they feel this morning!
あ… どんな感じも何も…
I didn't notice anything unusual.
Did you tighten or loosen them!?
今朝 昨日に比べ釘と釘の間を
開けたのか閉めたのか？
They needed a little loosening, actually...
はあ それは… 若干 開けましたが
あ…！
ああ いえ　もちろん
They were still well within setting "C!"
設定Ｃの範囲内の話でして
Tight enough to block all but one of 150 or 200, never mind 100!
何しろ あのままだと 100に１つの
通過どころか 150か200…
やられた！それだ
He got us!
That's it!
I thought the same thing yesterday!
俺も昨日 全く同じことをした
店長 どこへ？
Where are you going, boss!?
あのガキ！逆発想
That punk kid!
He had the other idea, and it worked!
死角を突いてきやがった
He didn't mess with the Bog, he thought of something else!
沼本体の細工を不可能と見限り
全く別発想
And it ended up being... This!
あろうことか奴は こっち！
このゲージ棒の玉の方を細工して
入れ替えやがった！
He made a bigger gage, and slipped it in!
The setting "C" ball is even bigger than the setting "A" one!
明らかに設定Ｃの玉が
設定Ａの玉よりでかい！
And he made it bigger day by day so we didn't notice!
恐らく俺たちが気づかないように
少しずつ大玉に替えていったんだ
Dammit! With that big of a gap he can just shoot them straight through!
クッソー こんなので
調整していたら
そりゃあ ガバガバになる
だが どうやって…
But how'd he pull it off!?
There's only one door, and there's always someone nearby!
部屋の入り口は１つ
中には常に店の者が誰かはいる
ここに忍び込めるわけがない
He couldn't of snuck in. So how!?
だったら どうやって これを…
Wait, there's...
あっ！何だ これは？
What's this!?
コンクリの破片
Concrete dust!
Boss!
店長？
上だ 上
He came in from above! Go to the sixth floor, and check the room above us!
６階に行け！この真上の部屋へ
はあ？
この上は空き部屋だ！
Search the empty room there!
中を調べろ！
何もない
こっちだ
There's nothing here.
Wait, over there!
Did you find something!?
何があった？
あ… 穴が！
A hole!
There's a huge hole right over the office!
事務室のちょうど上と
思われる辺りに バカでかい穴が！
クッ… やはりそうか　分かった
I knew it. Thanks.
やられた　釣り堀だ
He fished them out!
釣り堀？
そうだ
Fished?
Yes.
Each day since the Bog came back, he's peeked down through that vent,
沼を再開してからの この３日
恐らく奴は この上の部屋から
そこの換気口を通じて
made sure no one was here,
作業を確認できるように
セットした
and fished up the "C" gage with an electromagnet!
そして多分 電気磁石を垂らして
Ｃ設定のゲージ棒を釣り上げ
He replaces the ball on the end with a bigger one, and returns it!
上で やや大きめの玉に交換し
再び戻す
このすり替えを
繰り返してたんだ 奴は
He's been doing this over and over!
Think about it! He's been in this room before!
思い出してみろ
この間 奴はこの部屋に入ってきた
あの時 ゲージ棒の置き場所が
He must have noticed we keep the gages under the vent!
換気口の真下にあることに
気づいたんだ
さらに俺とお前が１日交代で
釘のチェックをする
And he knows we alternate days checking the pins!
日替わり体制の弊害 不備を
突いてきた
That alternation is our ruin!
ああっ…
考えてみれば
Neither of us knew why the previous day's setting was so tight!
俺たちは互いに前日の釘の
閉まり具合が
どうなってるかを知っちゃいない
設定Ｃという標識に
ただ漠然と従っていただけだ
Knowing it was still setting "C" blinded us to the truth!
本当のことは何も
見えちゃいなかった　クッ…
We didn't notice at all!
フフフ… なっ？
面白いだろ なかなか
Not bad, huh?
沼なんかに触らずとも
細工はできるって話さ
I can even break the Bog without ever touching it myself.
自ら触ることはできなくても
I don't need to, when I have these morons doing it for me every morning!
毎日 律儀に調整してくれる
間抜けがいるじゃねえか
てっ 店長
Boss!
発動だ！ブロックを発動する！
Activate it! Activate the block!
人の目もクソもない！
潰すんだ 奴を！
I don't care who's watching! Bury him!
He's in the trays again!
きた！
きたぞ またクルーンに！
Go! Go go go!
いけ！いけ いけ いけ！
I need to do this before they activate the block!
奴がブロックを発動する その前に
決まれ！決まってしまえ！
It's now or never!
Holy crap!
おお すげえ！
I've never seen someone get two in the trays at once!
２個だ ２個！
こんなの初めて見たぜ
Go for it! You can do it!
きてる きてる！いけ いけ！
This is my chance! The second gate block is open!
チャンスだ！敵は２番目の関門の
ブロックを控えている
生きたんだ
この間のおっちゃんの大暴れが！
The old man's act did it!
インチキ！インチキ！
It cheats! It cheats!
You! You're the part that does it! Die!
諸悪の根源！死ねー！
あれが生きた！奴に隙を作らせた
It did it!
It gave me this chance!
これ以上 客に不信感を
持たれたくないという
I need to win while they're still hesitant to look like they're cheating!
隙 ゆるみを！
Go! Now!
いけ！今だ！この機に乗じて
ひねり込む！
Make it in while I still can!
あー 惜しい！
でもまだ１つ残ってる
Aww, man!
He's still got one!
Go!
いけー！
おー！
きたきた ２段目ー！
There we go! Second tray!
いけ いけー！
Go for it!
Go! Go!
あー！
惜しー！
Aww...
でも まだまだ！
イエー！
He's still in the game!
Go!
It's done.
完了です
よし
Excellent.
You're done, fool.
バカめ　ここまでだ
This will finish the whole mess.
これで この大騒ぎも終結 終わり
You'll never hit the jackpot. It's not even worth dreaming about.
大当たりはおろか
夢さえ見れなくなる
もう届かないんだからな
クルーンには！
You'll never even make it to the trays.
It's pointless!
不毛だ　不毛に銀玉を
費やして死ね！
Keep wasting your balls until you die!
死ね！死ね！死ね！死ね！死ね！
死ぬがいい！
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Go ahead and die!
He's not making it to the trays anymore!
行かなくなった　クルーンに
この間のオヤジの時と一緒だ
It's the same thing that happened to the old guy! It just suddenly stops working!
ある瞬間から
まるで行かなくなったんだ
はじくんだよ 全部あれが！
It's flipping all the balls away!
Not this shit again!
ひでえ またかよ！
きたねえぞ！
This is no fair!
Aim right!
右打ちだ！
おお そうだ
That's right!
この間 右に流してたら行ったぞ
If you aim right, you can still bounce them in!
No, wait!
いや でも…
The windmill's stopped!
風車が止まってる
Anything aimed to the right just drops!
右に流れた玉は
そのまま落ちるだけだ
The windmill used to spin!
この間は あの風車が
適度に回ってくれた
That's how it flipped the balls back to the middle!
だからこそ玉は
真ん中に運ばれもした
But now it's useless, even if he tries for a decade!!
今のこの風車じゃ あり得ない
10年打っても！
フッフッフ…
I've closed that off nice and tight!
対策済みさ その点は
だから締めたのさ
急所の風車をギュウギュウにな
回らぬ風車だ　どうするカイジ？
That windmill isn't going to spin! What will you do, Kaiji!?
What will he do?
どうする？どうする？
どうする カイジ？
What will he do!? What will Kaiji do!?
Ichijou stands in his way, wielding the killer block!
立ちはだかる一条
究極の必殺ブロック
Can he break through!?
あるのか 突破 勝利への道！
Is there a path to victory!?
あるのか？
Playing Ichijou, manager of the illegal casino, is Daisuke Namikawa.
Hi, KnT fans! This is Daisuke Namikawa!
Ichijou's clash with Kaiji is just amazing!
I'm trying my hardest to bring out depth, hidden strength, and passion!
It's really tough, but it's so worth it! I hope you all keep watching to the end!
Make Kaiji S2 yours!
KnT—Wait!
That's not it!